http://stephenhunt.net/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy: GDPR Short.
Personal Data collected for the following purposes and using the following services:
Analytics/Advertising
Google Analytics/Google AdSense.
Personal Data: Cookies and Usage Data.
Contacting the User
Mailing List or Newsletter.
Personal Data: email address and name.
Displaying content from external platforms
YouTube video widget.
Personal Data: Cookies and Usage Data.
Handling payments
PayPal and Stripe.
Personal Data: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.
Further information about Personal Data
Selling goods and services online
The Personal Data collected are used to provide the User with services or to sell goods, including payment and possible delivery.
The Personal Data collected to complete the payment may include the credit card, the bank account used for the transfer, or any other means of payment envisaged. The kind of Data collected by this Website depends on the payment system used.
Contact information
Owner and Data Controller
Stephen Hunt, www.StephenHunt.net
Owner contact email: info <-a.-t.> stephenhunt <dot> net
Latest update: May 21, 2018
Privacy Policy: Long
Who we are
This is the personal & private website for the author Stephen Hunt, the web address is: http://stephenhunt.net
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Who we share your data with
We do not sell, share or rent your details to anybody else.
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Our contact information
info <-a.-t.> stephenhunt <dot> net
Buy Stephen’s booksGet my books on Amazon,
Kobo, Apple
iBooks, or Google
Play. Become a Patron of StephenLoad up on a range of goodies exlusive to the fine creator-support system that is Patreon. Get yourself over to patreon.com/stephenhuntFree Readers Universe MagazineGet Stephen's Monthly NewsletterJoin Stephen Hunt’s Readers UniverseSocialTwitterFollow me on TwitterMy TweetsStephen Hunt’s SciFi & Fantasy
Stephen Hunt’s SciFi & Fantasy
The Stephen Hunt RSS feedRSS - Posts
Stephen Hunt’s steampunk
Stephen Hunt’s steampunk
Recent releasesStephen Hunt's The Pashtun Boy's Paradise
UK - USA - Oz - Can
Stephen Hunt's Empty Between the Stars
UK - USA - Oz - Can
2020 Stephen Hunt author. All rights reserved. Premium WordPress Themes.
